click4freestuff.com 2014-09-27

# Wifeadventures.com

WIFEADVENTURES is committed to protecting your privacy. WIFEADVENTURES will not release your personal data to anyone else without your consent. WIFEADVENTURES has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We only collect personal information from visitors to our Web site when they voluntarily provide it to us by completing our registration form or electing to use one of our services. In doing so, we may require visitors to provide us with information including, but not limited to, their name, physical address, email address, username & password.

We use cookies to save your preferences and to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. When you visit our site, we gather information that does not identify individual users. Cookies are used to track your IP address only for the purposes of tracking unique user sessions, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We merely use aggregate information along with other data to make improvements to and update our site for our visitors.

This site make its chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. When you post to our board(s) your IP will be recorded and will be visible to the administrator and moderators of this site.

This site contains links to other sites. WIFEADVENTURES is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other such websites.

Our online surveys do not record any identifying information except your IP address.

The following Terms and Conditions govern your use and access to WIFEADVENTURES. By accessing, using, printing, installing, or downloading any material from WIFEADVENTURES, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions are subject to change.

WIFEADVENTURES offer online entertainment, adult in nature, and which may contain graphic depictions, nudity, adult language, and descriptions of explicit sexual activity. You acknowledge that you are aware of the nature of the content provided by WIFEADVENTURES, that you are not offended by such content and that you access WIFEADVENTURES freely, voluntarily and willingly, and that your community standards allow you to view such materials no matter your age of majority. You must be at least 18 (21 in some states) years of age.

At any time, and without cause, subscription to the service may be terminated by WIFEADVENTURES or the subscriber upon notification of the other by electronic or conventional mail. When the member requests the termination, subscription fees are NOT refunded. Subscribers are liable for charges incurred by them until termination of service.

Your subscription will be automatically renewed at the end of your subscription period at the regular monthly or quarterly rate if not cancelled. Cancellations must take place no later than 24 hours prior to the renewal date of the membership to avoid renewal.

Should a refund be issued by WIFEADVENTURES, all refunds will be credited solely to the payment method used in the original transaction. WIFEADVENTURES will not issue refunds by cash, check, or to another credit card or payment mechanism.

Visitors who have any questions about out Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions, the practices of this site, or their interactions with this Web site, should visit the Customer Service section of this site. Alternatively you can contact us by electronic or conventional mail.
